Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this section on reference types, we looked at what is the difference between a reference variable
在关于引用类型的这一节中，我们研究了引用变量和原始变量之间的区别
and a primitive variable.
和原始变量的区别。
We looked at the different primitive types.
我们看了不同的原始类型。
We looked at a few reference variables, how they are stored in memory, how they are initialized, and how
我们看了一些引用变量，它们是如何存储在内存中的，它们是如何被初始化的，以及如何
does assignment and equality work with them.
赋值和等价是如何进行的。
We also discussed a few reference types which are built-in in Java.
我们还讨论了一些Java中内置的引用类型。
We talked in depth about the String class.
我们深入地讨论了String类。
We discussed a couple of alternatives for it: StringBuilder and StringBuffer.
我们讨论了它的几个替代品。StringBuilder和StringBuffer。
We also looked at a wide variety of puzzles which are related to String and we also discussed about
我们还研究了与String有关的各种难题，并讨论了关于
wrapper classes.
封装器类。
We discussed about the eight wrapper classes which are present in Java, which are exactly corresponding to
我们讨论了Java中存在的八个封装类，它们完全对应于
the eight primitive types.
八个原始类型。
We discussed why we need wrapper classes and also  a variety of methods which are present in the wrapper
我们讨论了为什么我们需要封装类，以及封装类中存在的各种方法。
classes as well.
类中的各种方法。
And, at the end of this section, we looked at LocalDate, LocalDateTime, and LocalTime APIs. We looked
在这一节的最后，我们研究了LocalDate、LocalDateTime和LocalTime APIs。我们看了
at different methods to get specific data from the date, to get generic data like leap year, or length of
我们看了不同的方法，从日期中获得特定的数据，获得通用的数据，如闰年，或月的长度，或年的长度。
the month, or length the year, and also we looked at different methods to compare with other dates as well
我们还研究了不同的方法来与其他日期进行比较，以及增加特定的天数。
as to add a specific number of days, months, or years to a specific date.
我们还研究了与其他日期进行比较的不同方法，以及在一个特定的日期上增加特定的天数、月数或年数。
This was one of the first sections where we tried to explore some of the inbuilt APIs in Java. Exploring
这是我们尝试探索Java中一些内置的API的第一节。探索
APIs can get a little boring at times, but it's very important to understand what you can do and what
API有时会有点无聊，但了解你能做什么，不能做什么，是非常重要的。
you cannot do
你不能做什么
and once you know what you can do, you can easily explore and try to find the right method to do that
一旦你知道你能做什么，你就可以轻松地探索并尝试找到正确的方法来做那件
specific thing.
具体的事情。
I hope you had a interesting time in this section.
我希望你在本节中度过了一段有趣的时光。
I'll see you in the next section.
我们在下一节再见。
Until then,
直到那时。
bye bye.
拜拜了。